Washington Area Performing Arts Video Archives (WAPAVA)
DC Public Library Special Collections
- Series 1
  - Gospel According to Fishman, The - Signature Theater, 2002-01-08 - 2002-02-24 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Personal History (Missing as of 9/09) - African Continuum Theater at AFI, 2002-02-21 - 2002-03-10 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Swan, The - Rep Stage, 2002-02-24 - 2002-02-24 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Company (Sondheim Celebration) - Kennedy Center, 2002-05-17 - 2002-06-29 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Duchess of Malfi, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 2002-01-23 - 2002-03-10 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Harlem Rose - Metro Stage, 2002-02-06 - 2002-03-10 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Sunday in the Park with George (Sondheim… - Kennedy Center, 2002-05-10 - 2002-06-20 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Sweeney Todd (Sondheim Celebration) - Kennedy Center, 2002-05-10 - 2002-06-20 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Little Night Music (Sondheim Celebration), A - Kennedy Center, 2002-08-02 - 2002-08-25 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Merrily We Roll along (Sondheim Celebration) - Kennedy Center, 2002-07-02 - 2002-08-24 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Passion (Sondheim Celebration) - Kennedy Center, 2002-07-19 - 2002-08-23 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Belle of Amherst, The - Rep Stage, 2002-03-15 - 2002-03-31 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Corpus Christi - Source Theatre, 2002-03-17 - 2002-04-13 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Prometheus - Studio Theatre, 2002-03-20 - 2002-04-28 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Romeo and Juliet - Shakespeare Theatre, 2002-03-26 - 2002-05-18 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - She Stoops to Conquer - Folger Theater, 2002-02-23 - 2002-04-07 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Silent Noisy Show, The - Discovery Theatre, 2002-03-12 - 2002-03-16 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Tommy J and Sally - Theater J and Woolly Mammoth, 2002-02-18 - 2002-03-24 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Floyd King’s Still Mad - Shakespeare Theatre, 2002-04-29 - 2002-04-29 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Hamlet - Stanislavsky Theatre, 2002-04-03 - 2002-06-16 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Last of the Thorntons, The - Quotidian Theatre Company, 2002-05-31 - 2002-06-30 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Polk County - Arena Stage, 2002-03-28 - 2002-05-12 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Sea Marks - MetroStage, 2002-04-25 - 2002-05-26 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Shakespeare, Moses and Joe Papp - Round House Theatre, 2002-04-03 - 2002-05-05 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Waiting for the Slow Dance and Precious Lam’ - Keegan Theatre, 2002-04-18 - 2002-05-11 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Dutchman - Source Theatre, 2002-06-01 - 2002-06-30 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Fresh of Breath Air, A - Gaithersburg, City of, 2002-05-23 - 2002-06-16 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Little Foxes, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 2002-06-04 - 2002-07-28 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Little Foxes, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 2002-06-04 - 2002-07-28 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Othello - Folger Theatre, 2002-05-09 - 2002-06-16 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Our Town - Round House Theatre, 2002-05-29 - 2002-06-30 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Amen Corner, The - African American Continuum Theatre Co., 2002-09-07 - 2002-10-06 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Born Guilty - Theatre J, 2002-05-19 - 2002-07-14 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Dairies, The - Signature Theatre, 2002-06-04 - 2002-07-14 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Peter and the Wolf - Theater J, 2002-05-21 - 2002-07-07 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Anna Lucasta - Rep Stage, 2002-09-27 - 2002-10-03 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Ariel Doffman, an Evening with - Corcoran Gallery and Theater J, 2002-10-07 - 2002-10-07 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Recent Tragic Events - Woolly Mammoth Theatre Co at Theater, 2002-08-19 - 2002-10-05 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Three Sistahs - MetroStage, 2002-09-05 - 2002-10-27 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Glass Menagerie, The (restricted viewing) - Keegan Theatre, The, 2002-10-13 - 2002-11-17 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Privates on Parade - Studio Theatre, The, 2002-09-11 - 2002-11-17 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Winter’s Tale, The - Shakespeare Theater, 2002-08-27 - 2002-10-10 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Women and the Forest - Shakespeare Theatre, 2002-08-27 - 2002-10-10 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Christmas Carol Rag, The - Signature Theatre, 2002-11-12 - 2002-12-29 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Death and the Maiden - Theatre J, 2002-10-03 - 2002-12-01 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Faith Healer - Rep Stage, 2002-11-01 - 2002-11-24 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Gospel of John, The - Theater Alliance, 2002-11-14 - 2002-11-27 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - 110 in the Shade - Signature Theatre, 2003-01-01 - 2003-03-09 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Christmas Carol, A - Round House Theatre, 2002-12-13 - 2002-12-29 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Cherry Orchard, The - Round House Theater, 2002-11-13 - 2002-12-08 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Host and Guest - Stanislavsky Theater Stuide and Synetic, 2002-10-31 - 2002-12-22 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - On the Bedpost Overnight with Jon Spelman - Washington Storytellers Theatre @ DCA, 2003-04-17 - 2003-04-26 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Jump/Cut - Theatre J, 2003-02-24 - 2003-03-30 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Much Ado About Nothing - Shakespeare Theatre, 2002-11-05 - 2003-01-15 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Silent Woman, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 2003-01-21 - 2003-03-09 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Twelfth Night - Folger Theatre, 2003-01-03 - 2003-02-09 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - 1776 - Ford’s Theatre, 2003-03-12 - 2003-06-08 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth the Queen - The Folger Theatre, 2003-03-22 - 2003-05-04 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Endgame - Catalyst Theatre Company, 2003-02-12 - 2003-03-23 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Good Thief, The - Warehouse Theater/Scena Theatre, 2003-03-09 - 2003-04-13 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Philanderer, The - Washington Stage Guild, 2003-03-06 - 2003-04-13 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Follies - Signature Theatre, 2003-04-01 - 2003-06-01 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - La Vagabonde - LeNeon Theatre, 2003-03-28 - 2003-04-20 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Play About the Baby, The - Studio Theatre, 2003-03-26 - 2003-05-25 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Return to Morality, The - Rep Stage, 2003-03-14 - 2003-03-30 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Richard II - Shakespeare Theatre, The, 2003-03-25 - 2003-05-18 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Bee - Asia Theatre, 2003-04-10 - 2003-05-03 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Mad Dancers, the - Theater J, 2003-04-29 - 2003-06-01 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Michael Kahn and Wallace Acton, An Evening with - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2003-04-21 - 2003-04-21 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Rose - Washington Stage Guild, 2003-04-24 - 2003-05-25 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Underneath the Lintel - Round House Theatre, 2003-05-01 - 2003-06-08 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - White Biting Dog - Project Y Theatre Company, 2003-05-07 - 2003-06-04 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Buried Child, The Shepard Project - Keegan and Fountainhead Theatres, 2003-05-15 - 2003-05-15 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Chekhov’s Jokes - Classika Theatre, 2003-09-27 - 2003-11-09 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Class Act, A - Studio Theatre, The, 2003-05-14 - 2003-06-22 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Count Basil - Horizons Theatre, 2003-06-05 - 2003-06-29 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Gospel at Colonus, The - Theater Alliance, 2003-06-12 - 2003-07-13 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Lie of the Mind, A - Keegan Theatre and Fountainhead Theat, 2003-05-08 - 2003-06-15 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Night of the Iguana - Washington Shakespeare Company, 2003-06-26 - 2003-08-10 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Patience - Woolly Mammoth Theatre, 2003-06-15 - 2003-07-30 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Crave - Olney Theater-Potomac Theatre Festival, 2003-07-16 - 2003-08-10 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Dear World - American Century Theatre, 2003-07-10 - 2013-08-09 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Donna Q - Signature Theatre, 2003-06-17 - 2003-07-27 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Monster - Olney Theatre Potomac Theater Festival, 2003-07-09 - 2003-08-10 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Off the Map - Round House Theatre, 2004-01-16 - 2004-02-01 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Talley’s Folly - Theater J, 2003-06-18 - 2003-07-24 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Life of Galileo, The - Studio Theatre, 2003-10-22 - 2003-12-14 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - No Man’s Land - Olney Theatre, 2003-07-16 - 2003-08-10 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Painted Alice - Theater Alliance, 2003-08-09 - 2003-09-14 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Piaf - Olney Theatre, 2003-08-10 - 2003-08-16 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Twentieth Century - Signature Theatre, 2003-08-19 - 2003-10-05 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Circumference of a Squirrel - Charter Theatre, 1997-10-15 - 2003-11-09 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Drawer Boy Post Show Discussion, The - Round House Theatre, 2003-10-10 - 2003-10-10 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Rivals, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 2003-08-26 - 2003-10-19 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Rough Crossing - Metro Stage, 2003-09-18 - 2003-10-26 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - A Delicate Balance - Fountainhead Theatre, 2003-11-11 - 2003-12-09 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - All’s Well That Ends Well - Folger Theatre, 2003-10-25 - 2003-11-30 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Dazzle, The - Rep Stage, 2003-10-31 - 2003-11-23 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Fool for Love - Rep Stage, 2003-09-26 - 2003-10-12 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Who’s Afraid of Virginia Wolf? - The Keegan Theatre, 2003-11-06 - 2003-12-13 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - A Midsummer Night’s Dream - Shakespeare Theatre, 2003-11-04 - 2004-01-04 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Cosi Fan Tuttle Goes Hollywood - The In Series at Source Theater, 2004-01-01 - 2004-01-31 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Hubert and Charlie - African Continuum Theater Company at t, 2003-11-14 - 2003-11-30 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Abduction from the Seraglio, the - The In Series at Source Theater, 2004-01-14 - 2004-02-07 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Allegro - Signature Theatre, 2004-01-06 - 2004-02-29 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Henry IV, Part 1 - Shakespeare Theatre, 2004-01-20 - 2004-03-13 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Jumpers - Washington Shakespeare Company, 2004-01-02 - 2004-02-07 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Lady Chatterly’s Lover - Washington Shakespeare Company, 2004-01-02 - 2004-02-07 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Crucible, The - Keegan Theater, 2004-02-19 - 2004-03-27 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Joe Turner’s Come and Gone - African Continuum Theatre Company, 2004-02-19 - 2004-03-07 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Melissa Arctic - The Folger Theatre, 2004-01-23 - 2004-02-29 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Vita and Virgini - Rep Stage, 2004-01-30 - 2004-02-22 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Arcadia - Rep Stage, 2004-03-12 - 2004-03-28 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Corcoran Gallery presents Arena Theatres: Designing for the Future - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2004-03-15 - 2004-03-15 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Homebody /Kabul - Theater J, 2004-03-01 - 2004-04-11 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Syringa Tree, The - Studio Theatre, 2004-02-13 - 2004-03-21 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Henry IV, Part 2 - Shakespeare Theatre, 2004-03-16 - 2004-05-16 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - One Red Flower - Signature Theatre, 2004-08-17 - 2004-10-03 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Women of Tennessee - Kennedy Center, 2004-04-12 - 2004-04-12 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Awake and Sing! - Arena Stage, 2006-01-20 - 2006-03-05 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Comedy of Errors, The - Shakespeare Theater, 2005-11-15 - 2006-01-08 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Cuttin’ Up - Arena Stage, 2005-11-04 - 2006-01-01 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Don Juan - Shakespeare Theatre, 2006-01-24 - 2006-03-19 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Fat Pig - Studio Theatre, 2006-01-04 - 2006-02-25 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Five by Tenn - Kennedy Center, 2004-04-21 - 2004-05-09 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Intelligent Design of Jenny Chow, The - Studio Theatre, 2005-07-30 - 2005-07-30 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Lady Windermere’s Fan - Shakespeare Theatre, 2005-06-07 - 2005-07-31 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Lorenzaccio - Shakespeare Theatre, 2005-01-18 - 2005-03-06 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Macbeth - Shakespeare Theatre, 2004-08-31 - 2004-10-24 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Othello - Shakespeare Theatre, 2005-08-30 - 2005-10-30 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Persians, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 2006-04-04 - 2006-05-21 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - 9 Parts of Desire - Arena Stage, 2006-09-29 - 2006-11-12 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Carol, A - Ford’s Theatre, 2005-12-22 - 2005-12-22 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Cyrano - Shakespeare Theatre, 2004-07-31 - 2004-07-31 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Disputation, The - Theatre J, 2005-08-31 - 2005-10-02 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Enemy of the People, An - Shakespeare Theatre, 2006-08-29 - 2006-10-26 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Love’s Labors Lost - Shakespeare Theatre, 2006-06-06 - 2006-07-30 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Pericles - Shakespeare Theatre, 2004-11-09 - 2005-01-20 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Picasso’s Closet - Theatre J, 2006-06-21 - 2006-07-23 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Shenandoah - Ford’s Theatre, 2006-05-29 - 2006-05-29 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Tempest, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 2005-03-22 - 2005-05-22 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Two Trains Running - Kennedy Center, 2004-11-04 - 2004-11-28 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Urinetown - Signature Theatre, 2005-08-16 - 2005-10-09 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Argonautika - Shakespeare Theatre, 2008-03-01 - 2008-03-01 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Carol, A - Ford’s Theatre, 2006-12-09 - 2006-12-09 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Coming Home - Atlas Performing Arts Center/Tribute Pro, 2006-11-12 - 2006-11-12 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Edward II - Shakespeare Theatre, 2007-12-28 - 2007-12-28 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Game of Love and Chance, The - Folger Theatre, 2006-04-07 - 5006-05-14 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Maryland Dance Ensemble - UMD Theatre Dept., 2007-11-30 - 2007-12-01 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Measure for Measure - Folger Theatre, 2006-03-11 - 2006-03-11 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Midsummer Night’s Dream, A - Folger Theatre, 2006-10-19 - 2006-11-26 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Nevermore - Signature Theatre, 2006-02-19 - 2006-02-19 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Physicists, The - OMD Theatre Dept, 2007-10-06 - 2007-10-06 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - State of the Union - Ford's Theatre, 2006-10-19 - 2006-10-19 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Tamburlaine - Shakespeare Theatre, 2007-12-12 - 2007-12-12 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Trying - Ford’s Theatre, 2006-02-11 - 2006-02-11 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Urinetown - UMD Theatre Dept, 2007-10-19 - 2007-10-19 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Ash Girl, The - University of MD Theatre Dept., 2008-03-04 - 2008-03-04 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Beaux’ Stratagem, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 2006-11-07 - 2006-12-31 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Dead Man’s Cell Phone - Wolly Mammoth Theatre, 2007-07-08 - 2007-07-08 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Hamlet…The Rest is Silence - Synetic Theatre, 2007-06-16 - 2007-06-16 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Helen Hayes Awards, The - Warner Theatre, 2007-04-16 - 2007-04-16 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - I have Before Me a Remarkable Document… - African Continuum Theatre Co., 2005-09-30 - 2005-09-30 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Jitney (re-edited) -, 2007-05-01 - 2007-05-01 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - King Lear - Folger Theatre, 2007-02-03 - 2007-02-03 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Macbeth - Synetic Theater, 2007-02-10 - 2007-02-10 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Measure for Measure - Folger Theatre, 2006-03-11 - 2006-03-11 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Meet John Doe - Ford’s Theatre, 2007-03-31 - 2007-03-31 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - One Destiny - Ford’s Theatre, 2007-05-09 - 2007-05-09 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Richard III - Shakespeare Theatre, The, 2007-03-03 - 2007-03-03 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Saving Almee - Signature Theatre, 2007-05-12 - 2007-05-12 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Taming of the Shrew - Washington Shakespeare Company, 2007-11-17 - 2007-11-17 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Titus Andrinicus - Shakespeare Theatre, 2007-05-05 - 2007-05-05 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Trouble in Mind - Centerstage, 2007-03-01 - 2007-03-01 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - 1 Henry IV - Folger Theatre, 2008-11-08 - 2008-11-08 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Clandestine Marriage, The - Ford’s Theatre, 2005-05-07 - 2005-05-07 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Curse of the Starving Class - University of MD Theatre Department, 2005-05-07 - 2005-05-07 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Filthy Rich - UMD Theatre Dept., 2008-02-23 - 2008-02-23 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Gil Mead: A Celebration - Kennedy Center, 2007-09-17 - 2007-09-17 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Hamlet - Shakespeare Theatre, 2007-07-28 - 2007-07-28 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Last Days of Judas Iscariot, The - Forum Theatre, 2008-04-26 - 2008-04-26 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Macbeth - Folger Theatre, 2008-03-29 - 2008-03-29 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Major Drama - Shakespeare Theatre, 2008-03-08 - 2008-03-08 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Maryland Dance Ensemble - UMD Theatre Dept., 2008-12-05 - 2008-12-06 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Nixon’s Nixon - Round House Theatre, 2008-06-28 - 2008-06-28 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Open the Door, Virginia! - Theatre of the First Amendment, 2005-05-05 - 2005-05-05 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Pangs of the Messiah - Theater J, 2007-07-22 - 2007-07-22 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - School for Scandal, The - Folger Theatre, 2008-06-07 - 2008-06-07 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Tempest, The - Folger Theatre, 2007-06-09 - 2007-06-09 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Anton in Show Business - University of MD Theatre Dept., 2009-02-14 - 2009-02-14 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Antony and Cleopatra - Shakespeare Theatre, 2008-06-01 - 2008-06-01 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Dog in the Manager, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 2009-02-21 - 2009-02-21 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Heavens are Hung in Black, The - Ford’s Theatre, 2009-02-21 - 2009-02-21 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - History Boys, The - Studio Theatre, 2008-04-27 - 2008-04-27 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Imaginary Invalid, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 2008-06-29 - 2008-06-29 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Ion - Shakespeare Theatre, 2009-03-21 - 2009-03-21 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Julius Caesar - Shakespeare Theatre, 2008-05-18 - 2008-05-18 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - One Country, One Destiny - National Theatre, 2008-06-01 - 2008-06-01 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Romeo and Juliet - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2008-09-20 - 2008-09-20 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - To Be Young, Gifted and Black - UMD Theatre Dept, 2007-10-06 - 2007-10-06 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Way of the World, The - Shakespeare Theatre, 2008-10-11 - 2008-10-11 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Angels in America - Forum Theatre, 2009-11-14 - 2009-11-15 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Design for Living - Shakespeare Theatre, 2009-05-23 - 2009-05-23 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Distant Country Called Youth - Kennedy Center, 2004-06-12 - 2004-06-12 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Glass Managerie - Kennedy Center, 2004-08-07 - 2004-08-07 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Goat, or Who is Sylvia - Bep Stage, 2010-06-24 - 2010-06-24 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - King Lear - Shakespeare Theatre, 2009-06-27 - 2009-06-27 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Liar - Shakespeare Theatre, 2010-04-17 - 2010-04-17 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Lisbon Traviata - Kennedy Center, 2010-04-11 - 2010-04-11 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession - Shakespeare Theatre, 2010-06-24 - 2010-06-24 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Much Ado About Nothing - Folger Theatre, 2009-11-22 - 2009-11-22 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Orestes A Tragic Romp - Folger Theatre, 2010-02-27 - 2010-02-27 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Price - Theatre J, 2008-04-06 - 2008-04-06 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Richard II - Shakespeare Theatre, 2010-02-21 - 2010-02-21 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Streetcar Named Desire - Kennedy Center, 2004-05-22 - 2004-05-22 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Arcadia - Folger Theatre, 2009-05-31 - 2009-05-31 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Between Trains - University of Maryland Theatre Department, 2008-11-16 - 2008-11-16 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Civil War - Ford's Theatre, 2009-04-18 - 2009-04-18 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Golden Age - Kennedy Center, 2010-04-04 - 2010-04-04 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Hamlet - Folger Theatre, 2010-05-29 - 2010-05-29 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Helen Hayes Awards -, 2009-04-13 - 2009-04-13 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Illusion - University of Maryland Theatre Department, 2009-04-26 - 2009-04-26 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Master Class - Kennedy Center, 2010-04-15 - 2010-04-15 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Orestes A Tragic Romp - Folger Theatre, 2010-02-27 - 2010-02-27 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Ramayana - Constellation Theatre Company, 2010-05-31 - 2010-05-31 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Rifarel Corazon - Teatro de la Luna, 2010-05-29 - 2010-05-29 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Trip to Bountiful - Quotidian Theatre, 2010-05-15 - 2010-05-15 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Winter's Tale - University of Maryland Theatre Department, 2009-03-01 - 2009-03-01 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - A Christmas Carol; Ghost Story of Christmas - Ford's Theatre, 2009-11-23 - 2010-01-03 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Alchemist - Shakespeare Theatre, 2009-10-17 - 2009-10-17 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - As You Like It - Folger Theatre, 2007-10-17 - 2007-11-25 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - As You Like It - Shakespeare Theatre, 2009-12-05 - 2009-12-05 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Black Pearl Sings - Ford's Theatre, 2009-09-25 - 2009-10-18 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Henry V - Shakespeare Theatre, 2010-02-28 - 2010-02-28 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Ivanov - Studio Theatre, 2004-12-12 - 2004-12-12 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Marisol - University of Maryland Theatre Department, 2010-05-01 - 2010-05-01 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Miser - Shakespeare Theatre, 2010-03-07 - 2010-03-07 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Much Ado About Nothing - Folger Theatre, 2005-10-20 - 2005-11-27 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Musical of Musicals - Metro Stage, 2009-08-27 - 2009-11-01 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - One Red Flower - Signature Theatrw, 2004-09-04 - 2004-09-04 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Romeo and Juliet - Folger Theatre, 2005-01-12 - 2005-02-20 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Seascape - American Century Theatre, 2009-08-22 - 2009-08-22 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - American Buffalo - Studio Theatre, 2010-06-12 - 2010-06-12 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Carpetbagger’s Children, The - Ford’s Theatre, 2011-01-29 - 2011-01-29 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Carol: A Ghost Story of Christmas - Ford’s Theatre, 2010-12-11 - 2010-12-11 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Fully Committed - Rep Stage, 2006-02-26 - 2006-02-26 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Hamlet - Rep Stage, 2006-04-08 - 2006-04-08 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Johnny Melste and The Switch - Oolas Nua, 2010-06-24 - 2010-06-24 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Lift: Icarus and Me - Theatre of the First Ammendment, 2006-02-04 - 2006-02-04 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Lost Ones, The - Spookey Action Theatre, 2010-01-04 - 2010-01-04 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - New Jerusalem: The Interrogation of Baruch - Theatre J, 2010-06-19 - 2010-06-19 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Oklahoma! - Arena Stage, 2010-12-18 - 2010-12-18 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - One Night with Fanny Brice - The American Century Theatre, 2010-11-20 - 2010-11-20 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Treadwell: Brigha and Dark - The American Century Theatre, 2010-06-19 - 2010-06-19 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Violet Hour, The - Rep Stage, 2006-11-20 - 2006-11-20 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Comedy of Errors, The - Folger Theater, 2004-04-14 - 2004-05-23 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Enigma Variations, The - Stage Guild, 2004-05-23 - 2004-05-23 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Helen Hayes Awards, The - Warner Theatre, 2010-03-05 - 2010-03-05 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Highest Yellow, The - Signature Theatre, 2004-12-05 - 2004-12-05 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Lenny and Lou - Wooly Mammoth Theatre, 2004-08-23 - 2004-09-26 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Little Shop of Horrors - Ford’s Theatre, 2010-03-12 - 2010-05-22 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Lord Arthur Savilels - Stage Guild, 2010-02-25 - 2010-03-21 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Monday Night with Bess and Tess - African Continuum Theatre Company, 2004-06-26 - 2004-06-26 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Odyssey of Telemaca, The - Theatre of the First Amendment, 2004-06-05 - 2004-06-05 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Rent - Reegan Theatre, 2010-01-30 - 2010-01-30 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Rivalry, The - Ford’s Theatre, 2010-01-22 - 2010-02-14 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Waiting for Godot - Shakespeare Company, 2004-05-22 - 2004-05-22 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Caroline or Change - Studio Theatre, 2006-06-14 - 2006-06-14 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Carol: A Ghost Story of Christmas - Ford’s Theatre, 2004-12-26 - 2004-12-26 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Columbinees - Round House Theatre, 2005-03-02 - 2005-04-03 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Copenhagen - Olney Theatre Company, 2004-10-10 - 2004-10-10 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Glimpses of the Moon - Metro Stage, 2010-10-17 - 2010-10-17 (Box 88, Folder 5)